ABOUT ME

I seek to be challenged. I love working with people and building teams. I am a quick leaner, and I believe that hard work, dedication, and positive attitudes lead to success. I am a mother to a wonderful two-year old with special needs.

EXPERIENCE

> KEY ACCOUNT REPRESENTATIVE

Solenis Canada ULC, Pulp & Paper Division • Jan 2020 - Present

Irving Tissue Company 2020 - 2021, Lake Utopia Paper 2022 - Present

- · Organized and executed high level trials and meetings
- Worked with various departments to organize and execute projects
- Provided regular written reports and proposals, managed inventory, made safety and process improvements
- Developed training material, lockout procedures and troubleshooting manuals for operations
- Successfully commissioned new equipment and applications

STUDENT UNION ORIENTATION CHAIR

University of New Brunswick Student Union • Jan 2018 - Nov 2018

Successfully planned, organized and executed Orientation Week for over 1000 new students

- · Interviewed, selected, and managed a leadership team
- Developed and presented training material to over 150 orientation leaders
- Developed an emergency response plan, detailed schedule, and execution plan for several events
- Developed sponsorships and partnerships with local businesses

CHEMICAL ENGINEERING STUDENT

Irving Pulp & Paper Division • May - Aug: 2015, 2016 & 2017

Summer Student Position - Irving Tissue 2017, Irving Pulp & Paper 2016, Irving Paper Ltd. 2015

- Provided technical support to operations and other departments through process improvement projects with a strong emphasis on safety
- Practiced data analysis and problem-solving skills to troubleshoot issues
- Coordinated between different departments as well as external contractors
- Developed skills in project management and effective written and verbal communication

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- Microsoft Office 365
- ParcView
- Pulp & Paper
 Experience
- Waste-Water
 Treatment Experience
- Laboratory
 Procedures & Analysis

LEADERSHIP

- Interpersonal Skills
- Organizational Skills
- Time Management
- Written & Verbal
 Communication
- Self-motivated & Selfstarter

CERTIFICATES

- Confined Space (2023)
- WHMIS (2023)
- CPR/First Aid (2023/2018)
- Lean Six Sigma White Belt Training (2015)

EDUCATION

University of New Brunswick

Sept 2014 - May 2019

Bachelor of Science in Chemical Engineering, Minors in Mathematics & Business Administration